<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="69">
    <author>apuehri</author>
    <version>1.0.1.0</version>
	
    <title>
		<en>FastNight</en>
		<de>Schnellere Nacht</de>
    </title>
	
	<description>
		<en><![CDATA[The night will pass faster than you think!

This mod sets the time scale once a morning and once in the evening on a certain time scale!
"Left-Shift" + "0" calls up the settings menu in which
the values can be changed. Settings are saved in the savegame.
In addition, with the keys "Left-Shift" + "7" / "Left-Shift" + "8"
a manual change of the time scale in finer steps is
possible! Buttons only works outside of vehicles!!
In multiplayer, the settings can only be changed by the administrator!!

Changelog 1.0.1.0:
 - Fix: Time scaling is not loaded correctly at game start
]]></en>

		<de><![CDATA[Die Nacht wird schneller vergehen als du denkst!

Dieser Mod stellt die Zeitskalierung einmal morgens und einmal abends auf eine bestimmte Zeitskalierung!
"Shift-Links" + "0" ruft das Einstellungsmenü auf in dem die Werte
verändert werden können. Einstellungen werden im Savegame gespeichert
Ausserdem ist mit den Tasten "Shift-Links" + "7" / "Shift-Links" + "8"
eine manuelle Veränderung der Zeitskalierung in feineren Schritten
möglich! Bedienung funktioniert nur außerhalb von Fahrzeugen!!
Im Multiplayer können die Einstellungen nur vom Administrator
verwaltet werden!!

Changelog 1.0.1.0:
 - Fix: Zeitskalierung wird nicht richtig geladen bei Spielstart
]]></de>

      <fr><![CDATA[La nuit passera plus vite que vous ne le pensez!

Ce mod définit l'échelle de temps une fois par matin et une fois
Dans la soirée sur une certaine échelle de temps!
"Left-Shift" + "0" appelle le menu des paramètres dans lequel 
les valeurs peut être changé. 
Les paramètres sont sauvegardés dans la sauvegarde
De plus, avec les touches "Left-Shift" + "7" / "Left-Shift" + "8"
un changement manuel de l'échelle de temps en étapes plus fines
possible! L'opération ne fonctionne qu'en dehors des véhicules !!
En multijoueur, les paramètres ne peuvent être modifiés 
que par l'administrateur !!

Changelog 1.0.1.0:
 - Correction : l'échelle de temps n'est pas chargée correctement au début du jeu
]]></fr> 
	</description>	
	
	<iconFilename>icon.png</iconFilename>
	<multiplayer supported="true"/>
	
	<l10n filenamePrefix="l10n/modDesc_l10n"/>
			
    <actions>
        <action name="fastnight_Minus" 		category="PLAYER"	axisType="HALF" ignoreComboMask="false"/>
        <action name="fastnight_Plus" 		category="PLAYER"   axisType="HALF" ignoreComboMask="false"/>
        <action name="fastnight_Setting"	category="PLAYER"   axisType="HALF" ignoreComboMask="false"/>		
    </actions>	
    
	<inputBinding>
        <actionBinding action="fastnight_Minus" >
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lshift KEY_7" />
        </actionBinding>
        <actionBinding action="fastnight_Plus" >
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lshift KEY_8" />
        </actionBinding>
        <actionBinding action="fastnight_Setting" >
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lshift KEY_0" />
        </actionBinding>
    </inputBinding>	
	
    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="Fastnight.lua"/>
    </extraSourceFiles>	
	
</modDesc>
